Hi Sharon?It's Debbie.Hi.
Hi Sharon? 我是Debbie. Hi.
Are you taking a vacation this summer?
你要休假吗 这个夏天?
I'm trying to plan Dean's going-away party.
我正在试着计划Dean 的告别派对.
OK.So you're away from August 10th to August 17th.
OK.所以你8月10号到8月17号不在.
Thanks.I'll let you know what the plans are.
谢谢. 我会让你知道计划是什么的.
So Simon,you'll be away in late August,
So Simon, 你会在8月底离开.
but not for long.
但不会很久.
Do you know how long?
你知道有多久吗?
OK.Thanks.
OK. 谢谢.
Hi Wendy.It's me.
Hi Wendy. 是我.
Will you be back from the Cape by the 30th?
你30号会从科德角(Cape)回来吗?
Great.Hey,did I tell you what James...
太好了.Hey, 我有没有告诉你James...
You'll be back at work on September 4th.
你会回来上班 在9月4号.
Thanks William.
谢谢 William.
I'll let you know what we're doing.
我会让你知道我们要做些什么.
Kevin.Kevin.
I didn't realize you don't get a vacation until November.
我没有意识到你没有假期 直到11月份.
I'm sorry I brought it up.
我很抱歉我提起它.
So what are you doing on September 6th?
所以你会干什么 在9月6号?
Uh huh.Kevin.Don't you dare tell Dean.
Uh huh.Kevin. 你可不许告诉Dean.